Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- B, 1883-1997; 4.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employes, 1960-1990 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employes: Pennsylvania Federation, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Marine Engineers, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of New York Railways Company Employees, 1918 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution, 1932-1947 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution, 1951-1977 (Box 7, Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution, undated (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution/By-Laws (District Council No. 8 - No. 19), 1959-1970 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution/By-Laws (District Council No. 22 - No. 28), 1929-1970 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution/By-Laws (District Council No. 35 - No. 48), 1964-1970 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution/By-Laws (District Council No. 52 - No. 76), 1969-1971, undated (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Constitution/By-Laws (Various Locals), 1962-1974 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Convention, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Directories, 1961-1968 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 9 (New York, NY): Agreements/Price Lists, 1936-1962 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 9 (New York, NY): Agreements/Price Lists, 1962-1969 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 9 (New York, NY): Arbitration/Litigation, 1943-1969 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 9 (New York, NY): By-Laws, 1924-1944 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 9 (New York, NY): Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 9 (New York, NY): Pamphlets and Publications, 1923-1979, undated (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: District Council No. 20 (Westchester County, NY), 1961 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Local 17 (Greenwich, CT), 1924 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Local 194 (Chicago, IL), 1916 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Local 490 (New York, NY), undated (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Pamphlets and Publications, 1937-1974 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America: Trade Union Committee to Defend Louis Weinstock., circa 1944 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1969-1976 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1980-1994 (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen: Constitutions, 1936-1959 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen: Constitutions, 1971-1979 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen I, 1937-1965, undated (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen II, 1937-1965, undated (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen: Constitutions, 1919-1935 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen: Constitutions, 1939-1946 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen: Constitutions, 1950-1960 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen: Debate Manual Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1970-1983, undated (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1925-1969 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees: Constitutions, 1919, 1943 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees: Manual It's Development and Structure, Constitution and Laws, Procedures and Objectives, and its Achievements, undated (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway of America, 1899, 1941-1978 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1926-1960 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Tailors, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Telephone Workers, 1937 (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Timber Workers, undated (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Utility Employees of America: Local 102 (Brooklyn, NY), 1935, undated (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Utility Employees of America: Local 103 (Flushing, NY), 1935 (Box 8)
  - Buffalo Central Labor Union, 1884 (Box 8)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council of Greater New York, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
  - Building Employees' Industrial Union of America, undated (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union, 1957-1966 (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union, undated (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Constitutions, 1940-1955 (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 2 (Window Cleaners' Union), 1945-1969 (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 32B (New York, NY), 1935-1944 (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 32B (New York, NY), 1961-1975, undated (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 32J (New York, NY), 1953-1991 (Box 8)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 74 (New York, NY), undated (Box 9)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 144 (Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services), 1974-1985, undated (Box 9)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union: Local 312 (Registered Nurses Guild), 1949 (Box 9)
  - Building Trades Council of New York City, 1883-1897 (Box 9)
  - Burlesque Artists Association, undated (Box 9)
  - Butchers, Food Handlers and Allied Workers Union of Greater New York and New Jersey, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
- C, 1885-2004; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Cabdriver's Brotherhood Association, undated (Box 9)
  - California State Employees' Association, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
  - California Teachers Association, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Cambridge Central Labor Union (Cambridge, MA), 1940, undated (Box 9)
  - Cambridge Union of University Teachers (Cambridge, MA), 1937-1939 (Box 9)
  - Canadian Airline Navigators Association: Constitution and By-Laws, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Canadian Congress of Labour, 1954, undated (Box 9)
  - Canadian Federation of Labour, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Canadian Labour Congress, 1956-1966 (Box 9)
  - Canadian Labour Congress, 1970-1976, undated (Box 9)
  - Canadian Seamen's Union, undated (Box 9)
  - Canadian Trade Union Council for Histadrut, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Canadian Union of Postal Workers, 1979 (Box 9, Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Canal Zone Workers Union, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Cannery and Agricultural Workers Industrial Union, 1940, undated (Box 9)
  - CAW-Canada (National Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers Union of Canada), undated (Box 9)
  - Central Council of Polish Trade Unions: The Life of Working People in People's Poland, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Central Council of the Hungarian Trade Unions (Hungary), undated (Box 9)
  - Central Federation of Labor, 1888, 1903 (Box 9)
  - Central Hudson Employees Association, 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Central Labor Council (Cincinnati, OH), 1924 (Box 9)
  - Central Labor Union of Brooklyn and Vicinity, 1885-1887 (Box 9)
  - Central Labor Union of New York and Vicinity, 1886-1888 (Box 9)
  - Central Organization of Salaried Employees in Sweden, 1976, undated (Box 9)
  - Central Trades and Labor Council of Rochester and Vicinity, 1904 (Box 9)
  - Central Trades Assembly, 1886 (Box 9)
  - Chartered Society of Amalgamated Lace Operatives of America, 1961 (Box 9)
  - Chicago Printing Trades Union, undated (Box 9)
  - Chicago Trades Union Label League, 1904 (Box 9)
  - Chicago Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and Vicinity: Local 705 (Independent), 1957 (Box 9)
  - Chinese Staff and Workers Association, 1987-1995, undated (Box 9)
  - Chorus Equity Association, 1926-1949 (Box 9)
  - ChristLichen Holzarheiterberbandes: Sozialdemokratifche Streik-Taktik (Cologne, Germany), 1905 (Box 9)
  - Cigar Makers' International Union of America, 1911-1965 (Box 9)
  - Cigar Makers' International Union of America: Local 22 (Detroit, MI), undated (Box 9)
  - Cigar Makers' International Union of America: Local 85 (Poughkeepsie, NY), undated (Box 9)
  - Circus, Carnival, Fairs and Rodeo International Union, undated (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1976-1981, undated (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists: Conventions I, 1972-1998 (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists: Conventions II, 1972-1998 (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists: New York Chapter, 1983-1998 (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) I, 1974-1991, undated (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) II, 1974-1991, undated (Box 9)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.): Conventions I, 1975-1986 (Box 10)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.): Conventions II, 1975-1986 (Box 10)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.): New York Chapter I, 1975-1986, undated (Box 10)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.): New York Chapter II, 1975-1986, undated (Box 10)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.): New York Chapter-Hispanic Committee, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Coalition of Telecommunications Workers Unions, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Columbia County Labor Union Council, 1937 (Box 10)
  - Committee of Interns and Residents (New York, NY), 1984-1985, undated (Box 10)
  - Committee for Maritime Unity (San Francisco, CA), 1946-1974 (Box 10)
  - Compressed Air, Free Air, Foundation, Tunnel, Caisson, Cylinder, Subway, Cofferdam, Sewer Construction Workers' Union Local 147 (New York, NY), undated (Box 10)
  - Confederación de Trabajadores de America Latina, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Confederación de Trabajadores de Cuba, 1945-1960, undated (Box 10)
  - Confederación de Trabajadores de Mexico, 1937-1939 (Box 10)
  - Confederación General del Trabajo de la Republica Argentina, 1940-1943 (Box 10)
  - Confederación Nacional del Trabajo, 1981-1988, undated (Box 10)
  - Cónfederacion Obrera Argentina, 1926 (Box 10)
  - Confederation Generale du Travail (Paris), 1902-1994, undated (Box 10)
  - Confederation Netherlands Trade Union Movement (FNV) (Federatie Nederlandse Vakbeweging), 1976, undated (Box 10)
  - Confederation of Christian Trade Unions of Belgium, 1958 (Box 10)
  - Confederation of Free German Trade Unions, undated (Box 10)
  - Confederation of French Christian Trade Unions, undated (Box 10)
  - Confederation of Haitian Workers, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Confederation of Italian Labor Unions, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Confederation of Trade Unions of Yugoslavia, 1950-1979 (Box 10)
  - Confederazione Italiana Sindicati Lavoratori, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Congress of Polish Trade Unions (London, England), undated (Box 10)
  - Congress of Trade Unions of the U.S.S.R., 1933 (Box 10)
  - Connecticut State Council of Carpenters, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., 1992-1998 (Box 10)
  - Construction Forestry Mining Energy Union, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Cooks and Pastry Cooks Association: Local 186 (Boston, MA), undated (Box 10)
  - Co-operative Street Railway Employees' Association of New Orleans, 1941 (Box 10)
  - Coopers International Union of North America, 1939-1946 (Box 10)
  - Council of White Collar and Professional Unions, 1938 (Box 10)
  - Culinary Workers Union, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- D, 1903-1990; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons
  - Danish Federation of Labor I, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Danish Federation of Labor II, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Department Store Employees Union: Local 1250, 1937-1947 (Box 10)
  - Des Moines Trades and Labor Assembly: Iowa Unionist, 1924 (Box 10)
  - Deutschen Holzarbeiter Verbandes (Berlin), 1912 (Box 10)
  - Deutschen Metallarbeiter Verband (Berlin), 1919, 1924, undated (Box 10)
  - Diamond Polishers Protective Union of America, 1904 (Box 10)
  - Diamond State Telephone Commercial Union (DE), 1951, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Diamond Workers' Protective Union of America, 1903, 1905, 1946 (Box 10)
  - Director's Guild of America, 1965-1989 (Box 10)
  - Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, 1962-1983 (Box 10)
  - Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America: Constitutions, 1962-1980, undated (Box 11)
  - Distributive Workers of America, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Distributive Workers of America: Local 1 (Museum of Modern Art, New York, NY), undated (Box 11)
  - Distributive Workers of America: Local 103 (University of Chicago), 1970-1971, undated (Box 11)
  - Distributive Workers of America: Local 104 (Yale University), 1969-1971, undated (Box 11)
  - Distributive Workers Union, 1950 (Box 11)
  - Doctor's Association of the City of New York, 1971, undated (Box 11)
  - Doctors Council, 1984-1990, undated (Box 11)
  - Domestic Workers Union, undated (Box 11)
  - Dutch Food Workers Union, undated (Box 11)
- E, 1905-1967; 1 linear foot in 1 record carton
  - Eastern Seaboard Apprenticeship Conference, 1962-1967 (Box 11)
  - Embroidery Workers' International Union of America: Branch 6 (Auxiliary Embroidery Workers Union), 1912 (Box 11)
  - Employing Plasterers' Association, 1905 (Box 11)
  - Engineering and Allied Trades Shop Stewards National Council (London, England), 1943 (Box 11)
  - Enterprise Association of Steam, Hot Water, Hydraulic, Sprinkler, Pneumatic Tube, Compressed Air Ice Machine and General Pipe Fitters of New York and Vicinity, 1930 (Box 11)
- F, 1881-1991; 1 linear foot in 1 record carton
  - Farmers Union of the New York Milk Shed, undated (Box 11)
  - Federacion Ferroviana, 1920 (Box 11)
  - Federación Libre de los Trabajadores de Puerto Rico, 1921 (Box 11)
  - Federación Nacional Sindical de Trabajadores Salvadoreños, undated (Box 11)
  - Federación Obrera Regional Argentina, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Federacion Sindical de Trabajadores Bancarios de Cuba, undated (Box 11)
  - Federación Sindical de Trabajadores Telefónicos de Cuba, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Federated Ironworkers Association of Australia, undated (Box 11)
  - Federated Trades of Reading (Reading, PA), undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Unions of Algerian Workers, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians I, 1934-1946, 1986, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians II, 1934-1946, 1986, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Federation Technical School, 1943-1948, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Meeting Minutes, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians International Union, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Arts Unions, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand Workers of America, 1940-1952 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Greek Maritime Unions, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Independent Associations and Unions of El Salvador, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Long Line Telephone Workers, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Nurses and Health Professionals, 1986, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Organized Trades and Labor Unions, 1881-1887 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Printing and Kindred Trades of New York City and Vicinity, 1892 (Box 11)
  - Federation of South African Trade Unions, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Teachers' Organizations of Central America, 1985, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Union Representatives, 1960-1961, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of University Employees: Local 34 (New Haven, CT) I, 1984-1985, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of University Employees: Local 34 (New Haven, CT) II, 1984-1985, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of University Employees: Local 35 (Yale University Employees), 1974, undated (Box 11)
  - Federation of Utility Employees, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Federation of Women High School Teachers (Chicago, IL), 1934 (Box 11)
  - Fife, Kinross and Clackmannon Mineworkers' Association (Scotland), 1929 (Box 11)
  - Flight Engineers' International Association, 1961-1962 (Box 11)
  - Food, Tobacco, Agriculture and Allied Workers Union of America, 1944-1947 (Box 11)
  - Food, Tobacco, Agriculture and Allied Workers Union of America, 1947, undated (Box 11)
  - Foreman's Association of America, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Franklin Association of Printing Pressmen and Assistants of New York and Vicinity, 1890 (Box 11)
  - Fur, Leather and Machine Workers Unions, 1969-1984 (Box 11)
  - Fur Workers Union (A.F. of L.), undated (Box 11)
- G, 1904-1986; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons
  - Gasoline Station Attendants Union: No. 21530 (Boston, MA), 1938 (Box 11)
  - General and Municipal Workers Union (GMWU) (London, England), 1973-1981 (Box 12)
  - General Council of Trade Unions in Japan (Nihon Rodo Kumiai Sohyogikai), 1959-1961 (Box 12)
  - General Federation of Trade Unions (Great Britain), 1914-1916 (Box 12)
  - General Federation of Trade Unions (Great Britain), 1929-1986 (Box 12)
  - General Trades Union (Bulgaria), 1949, 1951 (Box 12)
  - General Union of the Algerian Workers, undated (Box 12)
  - General Workers Professional Union in Bulgaria, 1947 (Box 12)
  - German Federation of Trade Unions, 1951 (Box 12)
  - German Trade Union Federation, 1950, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, 1964-1977, undated (Box 12)
  - Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1940-1977 (Box 12)
  - Glass Warehouse Workers and Plant Handlers Union: Local 206, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee (U.S.), 1950-1955, undated (Box 12)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee (U.S.): Local 1735 United Office and Clerical Workers, 1954-1955, undated (Box 12)
  - Government Employes' Council, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Grand International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers: Constitutions, 1904-1924 (Box 12)
  - Grand International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers: Constitutions, 1936-1962 (Box 12)
  - Granite Cutters' International Association of America, 1941, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Graphic Artists Guild (New York, NY), 1976, undated (Box 12)
  - Graphic Arts International Union, 1974-1979 (Box 12)
  - Graphic Arts International Union, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Graphic Arts International Union: Local 251 (Atlanta, GA), undated (Box 12)
  - Graphic Communications International Union, undated (Box 12)
- H, 1910-2006; 3 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons
  - Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers, 1988-1992, undated (Box 12)
  - Health Professionals and Allied Employees (NJ and PA), undated (Box 12)
  - Hebrew Actors Union, circa 1940s, 2006 (Box 12)
  - High School Teachers Association of New York City, 1954-1960, undated (Box 12)
  - Histadrut General Federation of Jewish Labor in Israel, 1955 (Box 12)
  - Hong Kong Seamen's Union, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Hotel and Club Workers' Political Education Committee, undated (Box 12)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1943-1979, undated (Box 12)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Chicago Joint Executive Board, 1952, 1959-1970, 1974, undated (Box 12)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Constitutional Conventions, 1947-1976 (Box 12)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Constitutional Conventions, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Constitutions, 1943-1976 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 1, 1954-1979, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 2 (Waiters and Waitresses Union), 1946 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 5 Waiters Union, 1910 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 6 (Hotel Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, NY), 1945-1958 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, NY), 1963-1969 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, NY), 1978-1999, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, NY): By-Laws, 1941-1979 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 11, 1968, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 16, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 25 (Chicago Dining Room Employees, Merged with Local 356, 1960-1963, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 42 (Chicago Dining Room Employees, Cooks, and Bartenders), 1976, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 60 (Delicatessen and Restaurant Countermen Union), 1962, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 71, 1969 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 88 Minutes and News Clippings (Cooks and Pastry Cooks) (Chicago, IL), 1947-1962 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 89 (Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks and Assistants) (New York, NY), 1952, 1967, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 135, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 278 (Chicago Bartenders and Beverage Dispensers), late 1950s-1970s (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 302 (Cafeteria Employees Union), 1960-1969 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 471, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 593, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Local 610, 1976 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: New York State Council, 1962-1966 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: San Francisco Local Joint Executive Board of Culinary Workers, Bartenders and Hotel, Motel and Club Service Workers, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1939-1940, undated (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America: Chicago Joint Executive Board, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America: Local 88, 1946 (Box 13)